Synced by Uncle Frank
(slow, ominous music)
Welcome back to the program.
If you're just tuning
in, I'm sitting here live
with the sole survivor of
the Miles County Massacre,
Which occurred exactly one year ago today.
I've worked on this show for many years
and I've never sat across from someone.
Who has a story to tell quite like yours.
Thank you again for taking the time.
To sit down and speak with me.
[Survivor] It's my pleasure.
Now when we left off we were talking.
About the moment you
woke up from the coma.
Do you remember your initial reaction.
When you first saw your face?
[Survivor] Yes.
Would you like to share that with us?
(dramatic music)
I wished I was dead.
Do you still feel that way?
People are frightened
by the way that I look,
especially children.
And it's really difficult
for me to deal with that,
So isolation is ideal.
Now what about your attacker,
A man identified only as Art the Clown?
There's a lot of controversy
surrounding his supposed death.
The authorities issued
a statement claiming
that his body disappeared from
the county coroner's office.
The morning after the attack.
He's dead.
I saw it happen.
(glass shattering)
(dramatic rock music)
Did you watch it?
Oh my God, I thought she
was going to attack me.
(dramatic music)
(people talking)
My heart was pounding the entire time.
Yeah well, if you think she
looks that bad on television,
Imagine what she looks like
sitting two feet away from you.
I thought I was going to gag at one point.
Babe, do me a favor.
If I ever look like that, promise me.
You'll put me out of my misery.
You think I'm kidding?
I'll do it myself.
Yeah, Tom said we won't
know until the morning.
But he thinks the ratings
are going to go up big time.
(rustling)
(laughs) Exactly.
We've finally figured out
the formula for success,
Faceless victims and a host in jeopardy.
(slow, ominous music)
Yeah, watch next month, it's going.
To be called Monica's House of Horrors.
Shit.
Hey, can I call you back?
I have like 50 people calling me.
Okay-
Alright, love you too.
Bye.
Hello?
Tom?
(rustling)
(slow, ominous music)
(yelling) (screaming)
(squelching)
(slow, ominous music)
(staggered breathing)
(coughing)
(laughing)
(tense, dramatic music)
[Dawn] I think I just twisted my ankle.
Dawn, really?
Thanks a lot, by the way.
For what?
Promising you weren't
gonna get shit faced tonight.
Guys kept buying me drinks.
I can't help it if people
find me interesting.
Yeah.
Definitely your mind that they were after.
Who are you texting?
None of your business.
You gave that asshole
your number, didn't you?
Oh my god, you're so jealous.
Of what?
That kid was talking to
like five other girls.
Oh, stop being such a bitch.
Just get in the car.
Oh, you are not driving.
I'm fine.
Give me the keys.
Dawn, I don't feel like dying tonight.
Really?
Are we really gonna do this right now?
Give me the keys.
I'm gonna paw at you like a cat.
Give me what I want.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
You drive.
(chuckling) Thank you.
(wind blowing)
(slow, ominous music)
I'm fucking lit.
(laughing)
But if I get something to
eat, I can drive us, okay?
There's a place that's
open late, we can sober up.
[Dawn] Did you say food?
I said food.
You know the place, it's
right there, come on.
Okay, okay, Okay-
Just like give me one minute.
Fuck me.
Like one minute, for real.
(slow, ominous music)
D.
(E)-
- What?
[Tara] Look.
[Dawn] Holy shit.
Yeah, that's not funny.
I'm about to scream.
Hey, handsome.
Dawn, cut it out.
My friend wants your number.
I'm gonna fucking kill you.
[Dawn] Come buy us dinner.
Stop-
Just shut the fuck up.
Or what?
Maybe he'll drive us home.
I'm sorry, she's drunk.
(slow, ominous music)
Let's go.
Come on.
Let's just go.
(keys jangling)
(upbeat pop rock music)
Oh yeah?
You get dressed up?
Oh, you're a sick fuck.
Where am I gonna go?
Back to my wife?
Same shit.
Maybe another two hours?
Alright.
Alright, bye-
- Great.
(phone ringing)
Ugh.
That was the longest
piss I have ever taken.
Thank you for sharing that.
This guy wants me to meet
him at his apartment right now.
What a shocker.
I told him I would.
What?
I'm kidding.
I have a little more
self respect than that.
If you only had a brain.
I've been wanting to
use that one all night.
Congratulations.
(chuckling)
(rock music)
Look it's your boyfriend.
I told you this a week ago,
we'll go to your mother's.
I don't know, six weeks from now.
I'll be right with you buddy.
You gotta see the shape of this fuckin'
guy that just walked in.
(slow, ominous music)
' [Dawn] Are you okay?
I think we should get our food to go.
Why?
(slow, ominous music)
Him?
Seriously, I wanna leave.
Jesus Christ.
D, stop-
- Uh, excuse me?
Excuse me?
Can I get a picture with you?
Dawn, come on.
Shut up.
Hello?
(snapping)
Okay-
I'm gonna take that as a yes.
(slow, ominous music)
(popping) Oh.
Oh.
Sorry.
(phone ringing)
(slow, ominous music)
Thanks.
What the hell is wrong with you?
What?
Did you think he was gonna hack me up
into little pieces or something?
What can I get for you buddy?
Hey?
Hello?
(slow, ominous music)
If you don't order anything,
you're gonna have to leave.
You already have eight likes.
Can you hear me in there?
Oh god, it's gonna be a long night.
(slow, ominous music)
(cranking)
Aww.
(slow, ominous music)
(Dawn giggling)
What are you doing?
Thanks.
(Dawn chuckling)
Okay, not for nothing,
but that's the nicest thing.
A guy's done for you all night.
Seriously?
What the fuck?
Here you go ladies.
Yes.
You two okay?
Oh, he's harmless.
You okay?
Don't worry, I'll take care of him.
Enjoy your pizza.
(slow, ominous music)
What do you keep staring at?
That bag.
What do you think is in it?
I don't know, who cares?
Just eat your food.
You fuckin' freak!
Get over here.
All night with you, you fuck.
Enough.
(tense, dramatic music)
Get outta here.
Take your shit, and don't come back.
(tense, dramatic music)
Ramon, grab a mob and some bleach.
Eh, you okay?
[Man] Yeah, I'm alright.
(slow, ominous music)
[Dawn] What do you think
that guy did in there?
[Tara] Who knows.
[Dawn] Probably jizzed
all over the place,
fucking pervert.
' [Tara] Stop.
What?
I'm telling you that guy
totally whacked off in there.
He was obviously turned on by you.
You're fuckin' sick.
You know that?
(dogs barking)
What?
- Look at your hand.
- Oh, Jesus Christ.
Look, at least he had the courtesy to do.
Whatever he did in private.
I mean, he could have
whipped it out right there.
I really don't need the visual.
[Dawn] Well are you okay to drive?
Yeah, trust me, that
sobered me right the fuck up.
- Oh my god.
- What?
Your tire.
Fuck me.
Has it been like this the whole time?
I think I would have said
something if I'd noticed.
That your tire had exploded.
Why does this shit always happen to me?
[Tara] Do you have a spare?
It's on the car.
Wow.
I'm starting to feel sick.
Just, give me your phone.
I'll call my sister.
(slow, ominous music)
Yo Steve, this is sick.
I better get overtime for this.
No joke, this is disgusting.
You got me cleanin' piss
and shit at one o'clock.
In the morning.
Let the guy who handles
food take care of it,
Real fuckin' sanitary.
Steve, time and a half, or I'm out.
You hear me?
(rock music)
(phone ringing)
Hello?
[Tara] Hi, it's me.
Tara?
Yeah, my phone died.
I'm calling from Dawn's.
Ah.
Your phone died.
Can you ever go out
without using social media.
Every 30 seconds?
I think you're the only one in America.
Who has that sort of restraint.
Yeah, that's probably right.
[Tara] Did I wake you?
No, I am studying for
my midterm tomorrow.
Oh, shit.
Why, what is it?
What is it, Tara?
Dawn and I are sort
of stranded right now.
She has a flat tire and no spare.
And I was kind of hoping
you could pick us up?
I have to be up in five hours, Tara.
Yeah, I know Vic.
Don't bother, seriously.
I didn't realize you had a test.
(laughing)
Sorry.
I didn't know you were here.
(rock music)
You know what?
I gotta stretch my legs
and besides, if I fail,
I can always blame you.
You are the best sister in the world.
Yeah.
Where are you?
What's wrong?
I'm fine.
Why?
You keep looking over your shoulder.
Just thinking.
About?
Nothing.
Tell me.
What if that guy did this to your car?
What guy?
The clown?
[Tara] I'm serious.
Well, you really think
someone slashed my tires?
Well, he knows this is your car.
He saw us getting into it earlier.
That's fucking ridiculous.
I probably just ran over
a nail or something.
I should have just let you drive.
Yeah, you should have.
But as usual, you have
to be the good Samaritan
so here we are.
Stuck.
Like a couple of assholes.
(chuckling)
(slow, ominous music)
Steve!
(dramatic music)
Oh fuck!
(tense, dramatic music)
Help!
Somebody! (Phone ringing)
(tense, dramatic music)
(screaming)
(stabbing)
(gasping)
Yeah, but what if I'm right,
And he's out there watching us right now?
(gasping)
Show him your tits.
I don't know, Tara.
Look, that guy was harmless.
He's just some douchebag in a costume.
Acting like a retard
because it's Halloween.
(stabbing) (yelling)
No.
He was different.
(stabbing) (yelling)
He smiled.
The way he kept staring at
us with those dead eyes.
(stabbing)
What was in that bag?
(tense, dramatic music)
I don't know, Tara.
The point is, he's gone,
And you're never gonna see him again.
So cut the shit, 'cause you're
starting to freak me out.
I really have to pee.
So go.
_ Go?
Go where?
It's the middle of the night.
I can't just pop a squat
in the middle of the street.
And pee like you do.
Well tough shit, because
it's gonna be a while.
Before your sister gets here.
Fuck.
(deeply exhaling)
Maybe that guy has a
bathroom that you can use.
_ who?
That creepy guy who just got out of that.
Even creepier looking building.
Tara.
I was kidding.
Excuse me?
_ Yes?
I'm sorry to bother you.
Is there a bathroom in there I could use?
Sorry, I don't own the place.
I'm not supposed to let anyone in here.
Please, mister, it's an emergency.
I'll be two seconds.
Honestly, I could get
in a lot of trouble.
Who's gonna know?
[Dawn] Just let her use
the bathroom, for god sakes.
She'll make it worth your while.
A friend of yours?
Yeah, I'm sorry, she's drunk.
It's been a long night.
Alright.
Just make it quick, okay?
Thank you.
Guy's even weirder
looking than the clown was.
This way.
Good thing you called me when I did.
I was about to bomb the
hell out of this place.
Bomb?
Bug bomb.
Pest control.
What kind of pest?
You sure you want me to tell you before
you use the bathroom?
Why?
Don't tell me it's roaches.
It's not roaches.
Oh good.
[Mike] It's rats.
Rats?
(toilet flushing)
All clear.
Are you sure?
Rat free.
What if one crawls out of the toilet?
I'd make it quick if I were you.
Good plan.
Do you need me to wait for you or?
I'll be alright.
[Mike] You remember how we came in?
I remember.
_ Okay-
Well, um, you have a nice night then.
You too.
Thanks again.
Don't mention it.
(slow, ominous music)
(water dripping)
(deeply exhaling)
(howling)
[Man On Radio] Craven's
Halloween Super Store,
the brand new Halloween
super store with over
10,000 square feet of
costumes, accessories,
And decorations.
Miles County's largest Halloween store.
Kid's costumes, adult costumes,
Wigs, hats, and masks.
Makeup, and so much more.
So come in and check
out our huge selection.
Located at Roma Boulevard.
[Radio Announcer] This is
a WNEW breaking news alert.
We have a major development
in Miles County this evening,
Where authorities are
investigating a double homicide.
Two employees at the Deer Hill's Pizzeria.
Were found brutally
murdered just moments ago.
No suspects are in custody yet
but police are on the look out
for a tall, thin man
wearing a black and white.
Clown costume and carrying
a large garbage bag.
No way.
[Radio Announcer] An
eyewitness spotted the suspect.
After hearing multiple screams.
No further details at this moment.
Stay tuned, and we'll
continue to bring you.
More breaking updates as
they become available.
(police siren blaring)
(radio blaring)
(car door opening)
Oh my god, you're
never gonna believe what
I just heard on the radio.
(dramatic music)
(screaming)
(rock music)
(slow, ominous music)
(cat wailing)
(door opening)
(slow, ominous music)
(scoffing)
Figures.
(cat wailing)
(gasping)
Oh, I'm sorry.
Shh.
You don't have to say a word.
Your eyes tell me everything.
I didn't mean to frighten you, dear.
You must be the new tenant.
It's nice to finally meet you.
You're really going to like it here.
Isn't she, Emily?
This is my daughter, Emily.
Say hello to the pretty young lady.
It's been quite a while
since we've had neighbors.
Perhaps we can do our laundry together.
I could use some good company.
Yes.
That sounds like a good idea.
Will you excuse me a moment?
I have to find the landlord.
The first month's rent is due
and I don't wanna be late.
Punctuality is the thief of time, dear.
(slow, ominous music)
(heavy breathing)
(dramatic music)
(yelling)
(grunting) (Pounding on door)
(heavy breathing)
(door opening)
(tense, dramatic music)
(dramatic music)
(scratching on window)
(tense, dramatic music)
(heavy breathing)
(creaking)
(slow, ominous music)
(rustling) (slow, ominous music)
(stabbing) (screaming)
(hitting)
(screaming)
(stabbing)
(hitting)
(grunting)
(stabbing)
(heavy breathing)
' Help!
Somebody!
Please!
(heavy breathing)
(slow, tense music)
(rat squeaking)
(Pinging) (dramatic music)
(ragged breathing)
(heavy breathing)
[Radio Announcer] Happy
Halloween boys and ghouls.
The current temperature
is a crisp 43 degrees.
The winds are starting to pick up as well,
Setting the tone for old Samhain.
Now if you're still out and about in
the Miles County Area, I'd
advise you to be extra careful
out there.
Police are still on the look out
for a man involved in a brutal slaying.
Of two employees at Deer
Hill's Pizzeria this morning.
The suspect was last seen wearing
a black and white clown costume.
With matching face paint.
If you're just tuning in, this is not
a Halloween prank.
The local sheriff has advised all persons
in the Miles County Area to stay indoors
and notify authorities if they see anyone.
Matching the assailant's description.
' Really?
(slow, ominous music)
(heavy breathing)
(chains rattling)
(slow, ominous music)
(grunting)
(rock music)
Mister!
Help me, please.
(heavy breathing) (rock music)
Mister!
(dramatic music)
(rock music)
(muffled screaming)
(dramatic music)
(slow, ominous music)
(chains rattling)
(heavy breathing)
(tense, dramatic music)
(muffled yelling)
(dramatic music)
(slow, tense music)
(muffled screaming)
(dramatic music)
(muffled sobbing)
(slow, tense music)
(dramatic music)
(muffled screaming)
(ripping)
(sawing) (muffled screaming)
(muffled screaming) (squelching)
(Plopping)
(muffled screaming)
(muffled grunting)
(squelching)
(breaking)
(tense, dramatic music)
(hitting)
(yelling) (stabbing)
(gasping)
(crashing)
(heavy breathing)
(tense, dramatic music)
(slow, tense music)
(hitting) (grunting)
(clanking)
(grunting)
(hitting) (grunting)
(slow, tense music)
Come on, motherfucker!
Come on!
(heavy breathing)
(slow, tense music)
Get up!
Get the fuck up!
(slow, tense music)
(gunshot) (yelling)
(blood squelching)
(screaming)
(slow, ominous music)
(Tara screaming)
Shh.
It's alright, mommy.
It's only the wind.
It can't hurt you.
I won't let anything hurt you.
(heavy breathing) (yelling)
(gunshot) (yelling)
(heavy breathing) (tense music)
(gunshot)
I guess the new neighbors weren't such.
A good idea after all.
(humming) (slow, ominous music)
(gasping)
(gun clicking)
(heavy breathing)
(tense, dramatic music)
(knocking)
(clicking)
(phone ringing)
(tense, dramatic music)
(wind blowing)
(phone buzzing)
(slow, ominous music)
(tense, dramatic music)
(phone clicking)
(gasping)
(gunshot)
(gun fire)
(slow, tense music)
(heavy breathing)
(tense, dramatic music)
(rock music)
(dramatic music)
Jesus Christ.
Can you help me, please?
Who are you? How the
hell did you get in here?
You have to come with me now.
There's a dead woman in your basement.
What?
Yes.
Dead.
Dead, all dead.
He's killing them one by
one by one, like cows.
Look, lady.
Lady.
If you don't go away right
now, I'm gonna call the cops.
Yes, that's what I've been saying.
You need to call the
police right away because
he's right downstairs
and he's probably going
to kill you, too, if
you don't get somebody
down here right away.
What the fuck are you talking about?
The clown with the
white face and the little
black hat.
He thinks what he's doing is
funny because he's laughing.
But I know it's not funny
because they're all dead.
Get the hell away from me.
I'm telling you.
He knows I know, and he's
gonna try and kill me.
Before he kills you.
Don't touch me.
Don't!
Help me, please, help me.
I said, get the hell away from me!
(slow, tense music)
Emily.
[Victoria] Hello?
Is anybody in here?
What The fuck is going on here?
(slow, tense music)
(hitting)
' [Man] Wow.
Yeah, this better be good, man.
What happened?
You burn the place down?
Hello?
Mike?
Wow, you flipped out?
Hello?
Yo! (Smashing)
(smashing)
Tara?
Dawn?
Hello?
(slow, ominous music)
No.
Emily?
Okay-
You're scaring mommy now.
(slow, ominous music)
(staggered breathing)
Hello?
Anyone here?
Come on, you GUYS-
- Emily, mommy's here.
Where are you?
Emily?
Honey?
(slow, ominous music)
(rattling)
(banging)
Tara?
(staggered breathing)
(dramatic music)
Give her to me.
Please.
Don't hurt my little girl.
(dramatic music)
You're frightening her.
Can't you see that?
Emily?
It's okay.
Mommy's here.
(slow, ominous music)
Is there kindness in you?
Somewhere in your heart?
Have you ever felt a mother's touch?
Can you show no mercy?
She's all I have in this world.
Spare her.
(slow, ominous music)
(tense, dramatic music)
Shh.
It's okay.
(door closing)
(wind blowing)
(doorknob rattling)
[Mike] Hi, you've reached Mike.
Of course.
[Mike] Leave a message,
and I'll get back to you.
Mike, I'm outside.
Every fuckin' door in
this place is locked.
Answer your phone!
Asshole.
Hello?
Is anybody in there?
This is the fucking last time I do this.
No consideration whatsoever.
(phone ringing)
Dawn?
Hello?
Guys.
I know you're in there.
Dawn, I can hear your phone.
I swear to god, if this is a prank,
I'm gonna kill you both.
(dramatic music) (gasping)
(dramatic rock music)
(screaming)
(sobbing)
(woman screaming)
Tara!
(staggered breathing)
Can you hear me?
(staggered breathing) (sobbing)
(tense, dramatic music)
(screaming)
Oh, Tara, Tara, you're okay. It's okay.
I'm gonna get help.
What the fuck?
Oh, it'll be okay.
God, what's going on?
' Emily?
(dramatic music)
Help me.
(screaming)
(grunting)
Somebody please help!
Please!
(tense, dramatic music)
Help!
Somebody please help me!
(tense, dramatic music)
(staggered breathing)
(banging) (dramatic music)
(screaming)
(rattling)
Please, stop it!
No, please leave me alone!
(car horn honking)
Yo, Mike!
Son of a bitch.
You're on your own, buddy.
(truck starting up)
(slow, ominous music)
(staggered breathing)
Mike!
Hello?
(whistling)
(water dripping)
(slow, ominous music)
(dropping)
(scrunching)
(slow, ominous music)
(stabbing)
(sawing) (squelching)
(tense, dramatic music)
(kicking)
(bike bell ringing)
(slow, ominous music)
(door creaking)
(heavy breathing)
(squelching)
(bike riding)
(doorknob rattling)
(bike bell ringing)
(crashing)
(slow, tense music)
(dramatic music)
(bike bell ringing)
(crashing)
(slow, tense music)
(bike wheel spinning)
(rattling) (gasping)
(rats squeaking)
(slow, tense music)
(dramatic music)
(groaning)
(tense, dramatic music)
(dramatic music)
(hitting)
(gasping)
(coughing)
(tense, dramatic music)
(stabbing)
(yelling)
(heavy breathing)
(grunting)
(banging)
(tense, dramatic music)
Come on.
(Victoria screaming)
No.
(slow, tense music)
(sobbing)
You can't be dead, Tara.
Fuck, Tara.
Please wake up.
No, you can't be dead, Tara, look at me.
(sobbing)
(hitting)
(hitting) (yelling)
(heavy breathing)
I'm gonna get you out of here.
Come on, I'm gonna get
you out of here right now.
(slow, tense music)
(grunting)
Oh Jesus, you alright?
Stay with me.
I'm feeling a little tired.
I know, it's okay.
Just relax, it's gonna be fine.
(slow, tense music)
There's a phone over there.
I'm gonna call the police, okay?
_ No!
Please don't leave, don't leave me.
I am not gonna leave you, I promise.
I'm just going right over there.
Look.
(slow, tense music)
[Operator] 911, emergency.
[Mike] Uh yes, I need the police
and paramedics here right away.
[Operator] What's wrong, sir?
I wanna report a murder.
There's two dead people.
I've got this young woman over here
that's just been assaulted.
She's bleeding everywhere.
I think she's going into shock.
[Operator] Okay, give me your address.
[Mike] Uh, Steuben Street,
it's the old warehouse.
[Operator] What kind of
injuries does she have?
She's cut all over.
Some places really deep.
I don't know, she's
bleeding all over the place.
[Operator] Is she conscious?
Yes, she conscious, but I have no idea.
For how long.
[Operator] Where is the assailant now?
I knocked him out.
If this guy wakes up,
we are not safe here.
This guy is armed and he's
a total fucking maniac.
[Operator] Okay, sir,
what I want you to do now
is just remain calm and
stay on the line with me.
Until the police arrive.
Look.
We are not staying here.
I'm taking this girl
to the emergency room.
You just get your asses down here now.
I got my truck outside.
Can you walk?
(Victoria mumbling)
Okay-
Come on, let's get out of here.
(tense, dramatic music)
Dammit!
(dramatic music)
(screaming)
(hitting)
_ No, stop!
Stop!
(hitting)
(tense, dramatic music)
(hitting) (squelching)
(hitting) (yelling)
(tense, dramatic music)
(yelling) (hitting)
Dammit!
(dramatic music) (stabbing)
(gouging)
(tense, dramatic music)
(grunting)
(heavy breathing)
(dramatic music)
(yelling)
(ripping)
Get away from me!
Leave me alone!
You fucking maniac!
(bike horn honking)
Stop, stop it!
(heavy breathing)
(slow, tense music)
(sobbing)
(doorknob rattling)
(slow, tense music)
(police sirens wailing)
(tires skidding)
(crashing)
(jazzy music)
(door slamming)
(police sirens wailing)
(crashing)
(tires screeching)
(chewing)
Police, don't fuckin' move!
Put your hands up right now!
Central.
10-13, male perp.
Possibly armed.
Let me see your hands!
Send more units.
I said show me your hands!
Put 'em up!
I said put your fuckin hands up!
(police sirens wailing)
[Police Officer On The Left]
That's it, nice and easy.
No sudden moves.
Your right hand.
Show me the right hand.
Last warning.
You're gonna get shot!
(tense, dramatic music)
Do it!
[No, no]
(gunshot)
(tense, dramatic music)
Central, we got shots fired.
Multiple causalities.
We needed buses and immediate assistance.
(police radio chatter)
[Police Officer On The Left] Oh my god.
What?
(Victoria gasping)
She's still alive.
(police radio chatter)
(sirens wailing)
Aw, come on, guys.
You're killin' me.
The revolving doors won't
be installed until Monday.
Good to see you, too, doc.
[Coroner] Okay, what
are you bringing me?
Murder, suicide.
Wonderful.
What's behind showcase number one?
Severe head trauma.
You're probably gonna have to identify
this poor bastard by his teeth,
If you can dig them out
of the back of his skull.
So I should put on a seventh
pot of coffee, then, huh?
You're gonna need
something a lot stronger
than coffee.
Landon said they just
found two more bodies.
Jesus, they get the sick
fuck that's doing this?
Showcase number two.
No shit.
Police found him eating
the face off of some.
Young girl after he ran
her over with a truck.
He blew his brains out before
they could take him in, so.
Halloween never disappoints, does it?
And it looks like it's
just getting started.
Well, seeing as how I'm gonna be here
for another 24 hours, thanks to you,
you guys think you could
get me a breakfast sandwich.
With bacon, or something with bacon?
Bacon, really?
I thought you were
watching your cholesterol.
I am watchin' it.
Watchin' it go up.
Who's the MD around here?
How can you eat a greasy croissant while.
You're cutting up dead bodies?
Sweetheart.
I've been doin' this 22 years.
I've been doin this 22 years.
Alright, once you've
seen an eight month old
microwaved to death,
Everything else is just old hat.
Look, you had to ask, alright?
I'll hook you up, doc.
That's my GUY-
Stay safe out there.
(tense, dramatic music)
Jesus.
Let's have a look at the man of the hour.
(tense, dramatic music)
I hope your 15 minutes
of fame was worth it,
You sick son of a bitch.
(dramatic music)
(lights flicking)
(phone ringing)
[Woman] You're really
going to like it here.
(phone ringing)
(screaming)
(dramatic music)
(coroner coughing)
(coroner screaming)
(tense, dramatic music)
Thanks again for everything, doctor.
You'll be in our prayers.
Please, don't mention it.
We're all gonna miss this one.
She's been so cooperative.
Makes everyone laugh.
(laughs)
Well she certainly hasn't
lost her sense of humor.
Yeah, still a wise ass.
It's good.
It's a good thing.
It's important to stay positive, right?
Absolutely.
Good spirits.
She'll be fine.
Well, take care of yourself, Victoria.
I'll see you in a couple of months.
[Victoria] Thank you, doctor.
You're welcome.
So long, doctor.
Good bye.
What do you say kiddo?
You ready?
[Victoria] Yep.
[Doctor] Oh and, uh, good luck with
your interview tomorrow.
(slow, tense music)
(Bike horn honking)
(tense rock music)
(tense electronic synth music)